palgn.com.au 2007-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Australia's PAL Gaming Network

Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**   
PALGN will record any personal information that you provide to us. We will do our best to inform you if this information is going to be on public display or otherwise, however you must assume that all information you provide to us will be publicly viewable, unless explicitly told otherwise. 

**Storing Other Personal Information**   
PALGN may record other information such as IP addresses and visiting time in order to trace illegal activities (e.g. stolen accounts). IP addresses will only be available to our staff (administrators, moderators, editors). Any other information stored will be obvious if it is for public display or otherwise. 

**Third Parties**   
Any information PALGN stores will not be provided to a third party without giving you express permission to opt-out of the exchange. Some non-personal information is extracted and stored by third parties for statistical and traffic monitoring purposes. 

**Cookie Usage**   
PALGN will use cookies for storing information regarding your usage of the site. This will allow you to easily view our site and login to your personal areas. You may disable these from your browser. 

**Disclosure**   
PALGN openly volunteers the above information and any other such information pertaining to usage of the PALGN site. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to [feedback@palgn.com.au](mailto:feedback@palgn.com.au)

**Change to this policy**   
If this privacy policy is changed, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use, via the email you provide to PALGN. 

Catch up on PALGN's extensive coverage.
